Rohan Prajapati

Strathfield NSW 2135

Professional Profile

An enthusiastic and hardworking graduate from Federation University with a Bachelor of Information Technology. Currently seeking an opportunity in an IT related role to apply my academic knowledge and skills. I possess good knowledge of Java, HTML5, CSS3 and Microsoft Office which I learned during my university studies whilst completing university assignments and projects. I also offer good communication skills which I gained as a Retail Assistant for 2 years where I was involved in face to face interactions with customers.

Key Skills Summary

Programming Languages: Java, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3

Computer Systems: Windows XP/ 7, Linux Ubuntu, Windows 10, MacOS

Web Servers: MAMP/WAMP Server

Computer Software: Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access),

Eclipse, Android Studio, Visual Studio Code

Creative software(iMovie)

Education

Professional Year Feb 2020 - Present

Performance Education, Sydney

Key Subjects: Professional Workplace Writing, Australian Workplace Environment, Professional Meeting and Presentation, Applying Job Search Skills and Internship Preparation

Bachelor's in information technology

Nov 2016 - Aug 2019

Federation University (IIBIT), Sydney

Key achievements: High Distinction in Project 1 and Distinction in Project 2 and Programming 2

Diploma in Computing

Oct 2015 - Oct 2016

Sydney institute of Business and Technology, Sydney

Key achievements: Distinction in Business Information Technology, Introduction to Programming, Introduction to Software Design, Writing and Research for Science and Engineering

Rohan Prajapati

Academic Project

Shopping Website Development

Aug 2018- Sep 2018

Federation University, Sydney

Objective: To create a shopping website for a company as a university project that include interactive

user interface so people could perform features such as adding items to their shopping cart

Tools: Bracket, Visual Studio Code, Notepad ++, Pencil, Sketch

Duties: As part of a group project of 4, my responsibilities included designing the User Interface of the

website and some of the coding, which included designing the feature of linking the user to

the database of the website when they signed up to the website

Result: We were able to design a fully operative website with a good interface and was very

interactive. Achieved High Distinction in the first part of the project and achieved Distinction in the second part. I learned to use software such as Sketch and learned some codes for CSS3

and JavaScript

Employment History

Retail Assistant Nov 2018 - Present

7-Eleven Haymarket, Sydney, Australia

- Demonstrating strong communication skills by interacting with all customers on a daily basis
- Effectively stocking 5-6 items in their correct orders on the shelves on a daily basis
- Continuously displaying multitasking skills by interacting with customers, filling stock on shelves and cleaning at the same time, during each shift
- Displaying an extraordinary level of patience by handling 2-3 ill-tempered customers per shift
- Displaying effective time management skills by completing all tasks in the required time during each shift

Office Cleaner Sep 2018- Dec 2019

Assetlink, North Sydney, Australia

- Effectively communicated with the 4-5 office staff during each shift
- Constantly applied solid knowledge of health and safety procedures to my tasks during each shift
- Strongly demonstrated multitasking skills by handling 3-4 tasks on an hourly basis
- Demonstrated the ability to work autonomously and as part of a team, on a daily basis
- Frequently displayed good written communication skills by reading 5-6 lines of instructions on chemicals whenever new chemical arrived

Personal Attributes

 Demonstrated professional communication skills through 2 years' experience in customer service in 7-Eleven

Rohan Prajapati

- Strong time management and organisational skills developed through 4 years' successfully combining work and university studies
- Confident, experienced and resilient in delivering presentations and assignments during my university studies

References

Available upon request